sysaidit.com 2012-10-10

# Privacy Policy

SysAid (" **SysAid** " shall mean www.sysaid.com and entities controlling, controlled by or under common control with SysAid) is committed to safeguarding your privacy online for you, the user ("You" or "User"). Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as You make full use of SysAid's Services as further detailed in the Terms Of Use. This policy may be updated from time to time, therefore, SysAid asks You to check back periodically. Your continued use of the Services and SysAid's site after this Privacy Policy has been amended shall be deemed to be your continued acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for SysAid's website and describes the information SysAid collects about You and what may happen to such information. All capitalized terms and definitions in this Privacy Policy shall have the same meaning ascribed to them in Terms Of Use.

As described below, some of your personal information is disclosed to third parties and used by SysAid. By accepting the Terms Of Use, You consent to SysAid's use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information in accordance with the terms set forth herein.

1\. **Information that SysAid Collects**

1.1. **Registration Data**. SysAid may require You to fill certain information to provide services that You request, as they may exist in the Website from time to time (the " **Registration Data** ").

1.2. **Automatic Tracking**. By using SysAid's website, SysAid is able to and may track certain information about You and your correspondence on the SysAid site in order to perform internal research on its Users' demographics, interests, and behavior, as well as to monitor and enforce the terms of the Terms of Use. This information may include the URL from which You arrived, the next URL You may visit, what browser You are using and your IP address.

1.3. **Collecting Information**. Information collected about You will be kept in a specific file for You. SysAid may collect information about any activity being performed by You while using the Services, including any correspondence between you and other users of the SysAid site, messages left by You on any board or any searches and requests performed by You.

**2\. Children's Information**

2.1. SysAid's policy is that it does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from subscribers under thirteen years of age. The Services or site are not directed or intended for children under thirteen years of age. If you are under thirteen years of age, you should not register or provide personally identifiable information on the site. If you are the parent or guardian of a User under the age of thirteen whom you believe has disclosed personally identifiable information to SysAid, please contact SysAid at helpdesk@sysaid.com so that we may delete and remove such User's information from our system.

3\. **Cookies at SysAid**

****3.1. You acknowledge and agree that SysAid may use cookies on its site. A cookie is a piece of text that can be entered into the memory of your hard drive and can store information about your use of SysAid's Services (the " **Cookies** "). The Cookies will help SysAid make its services more convenient, personalized and more secure. In addition, Cookies may allow SysAid to keep track and retrieve information about any User who acts in contradiction to SysAid's Privacy Policy or its Terms of Use. If You would rather not have Cookies on your computer, You can usually set your browser to deny some but not all Cookies. You can also delete Cookies from your computer at your sole discretion.

4\. **SysAid's Usage of the Registration Data**

4.1. **Internal Use**. SysAid uses the Registration Data about You for internal purposes, to improve its site and to better tailor the site to meet Your needs. In addition, SysAid uses the Registration Data to analyze site usage and to deliver to You information about certain promotions, services or items that might interest You. In addition, SysAid may use your E-mail address to contact You regarding site notices from time to time. If You do not wish to receive such mailings, simply tell SysAid when You file your Registration Data with SysAid.

4.2. **Editing Registration Data**. You may review and edit your Registration Data by using your email address and Password. If You cancel your account, You may also have your Registration Data deleted from SysAid's database by sending your request to helpdesk@sysaid.com. However, You should be aware that once posted, You cannot change or remove any public postings made in SysAid's website. You should also be aware that even if you delete your Registration Data, there may remain residual information that will remain within SysAid's databases, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain personally identifiable information.

4.3. **Resolving Problems**. SysAid may use the Registration Data and other data it obtains from your current and past activities, to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems and to monitor and enforce the Terms of Use. In the event that You breach any of the terms of the Terms of Use, SysAid shall be entitled to use the Registration Data to locate You and pursue any necessary actions at its sole and absolute discretion in accordance with its Privacy Policy and its Terms of Use.

5. ** SysAid Disclosure of Users' Registration Data**

5.1. **General Rule**. SysAid will not disclose, sell or transfer any of your Registration Data to any third parties (e.g., advertisers or business partners), except in the following cases: (i) SysAid receives your permission; (ii) if SysAid believes in good faith that the law requires such disclosure or transfer; or (iii) as set forth below.

5.2. **Third Parties**. SysAid may at any time add business partners or co-branded sites to its site, but the sharing of information with them will be limited to only statistical information regarding Users in general, and SysAid will not disclose any of your Registration Data, correspondence or any related information. SysAid assures You that in the event that SysAid shall wish to transfer any of such information, SysAid shall notify You before transferring such information, so that You will always have a chance to object to such transfer.

5.3. **Special Cases**. SysAid may also disclose Registration Data or other information in special cases when it has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating SysAid's Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) SysAid's rights or property, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. In addition, SysAid may disclose Your Registration Data, in the event that SysAid believes in good faith that the law requires such disclosure. You thus authorize SysAid to disclose any information about You, it may posses, to law enforcement or other government officials if SysAid, in its sole and absolute discretion, believes that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate. Although, SysAid uses industry standard practices to protect your privacy, SysAid does not ensure, and You should not expect, that your Registration Data or correspondence will always remain private.

5.4. **Links and Displayed Sites**. SysAid's site may contain links to other sites and may provide access to other sites displayed as search results. SysAid is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such linked or otherwise displayed sites.

5.5. **Applicable Law**. SysAid's use of any information of a User is subject to the provisions of any applicable law.

6\. **User's Usage of Other Users' Registration Data**

6.1. **Use of Users' Registration Data**. SysAid's Services may allow You limited access to other Users' Registration Data, personal information or other information ("Users' Information"). Such Users' Information, if disclosed to You, is disclosed to You only for the purpose of using the Services in accordance with the terms and conditions of the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.

6.2. You hereby agree that You shall use any Users' Information only: (a) in connection with the Services, and (b) for any other purpose that the owner of such information expressly agrees to. In all cases, you must comply with any request by any user to delete any Registration Data of such user from your database. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this Section, may you disclose Registration Data of other users to any third party without SysAid's express written consent and the express written consent of the relevant user.

6.3. **Spam**. SysAid and its Users do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, You are not permitted to add any user, whose direct contact information was disclosed to you in connection with any use of the Services, to your mailing list without such user's express written consent after adequate disclosure.

6.4. **Password**. Your SysAid Registration Data is password protected so that only You and SysAid have access to this personal account. Since You may edit your account by using your email address and Password, SysAid recommends that You not divulge your Password to anyone. SysAid will never ask You for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email.

7\. **Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

SysAid's policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information SysAid collects from You. To the extent that You disclose information to other parties on SysAid's site or to any other third party, different rules may apply to the use or disclosure of the personal information that You disclose to them. Since SysAid does not control the privacy policies of third parties, You are subject to the privacy customs and policies of such third parties.

8\. **Message Boards**

Among the Services SysAid offers, Users may gain access to message boards. Any information which You may post to a message board, including any personal information, will be disclosed and available to all users of that message board, and is thus no longer private. SysAid cannot guarantee the security of such information, that you disclose or communicate in such message boards and you do so at your own risk. Any postings on a message board may be republished by SysAid elsewhere on the Web in any format.

9\. **Disclosure of Personal Information in the Event of a Merger or Sale of SysAid**

SysAid may merge or be acquired by another business entity or may sell all or substantially all of its assets to an acquirer. In the event of such merger, acquisition or sale, SysAid may share some or all or your Registration Data with the acquiring company in order to continue serving You and others and continuing to offer You the Services.

10\. **Security**

10.1. SysAid's site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the Registration Data. SysAid uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your Registration Data. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while SysAid strives to protect you Registration Data, SysAid cannot ensure the security of any information that You transmit to SysAid or any information that You receive from SysAid's Service, and You transmit such information at your own risk. Once SysAid receives your transmission, it uses its commercial effort to ensure security on its systems.

10.2. **Spam**. SysAid and its Users do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, You are not permitted to add any user, whose direct contact information was disclosed to you in connection with any use of the Services, to your mailing list without such user's express written consent after adequate disclosure.

11\. **Contact**

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of SysAid, or any related issues, SysAid will be pleased to assist You. You may contact SysAid at support@sysaid.com.

12\. **Subordination to the Terms of Use**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of SysAid's Terms of Use as an integral part thereof; in case of a contradiction between any provision of the Terms of Use and the content of this document, the provisions of the Terms of Use shall prevail.
